

#### CONTACT

**%** 805-588-9220

jennn.marshall@gmail.com

jennmarshall.herokuapp.com

github.com/jennnmarshall

#### EXPERTISE

Written Communication
Graphics Design
Planning
Collaboration

# SOFTWARE & LANGUAGES

HTML/CSS
JavaScript
SASS/SCSS
React
SQL/GraphQL

#### PERSONAL SKILLS

Creativity
Organization
Communication
Problem Solving
Attention to Detail

# JENN MARSHALL

# Full Stack Developer

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a former office manager transitioning into a software developer after completing my certification from the Full Stack Development Bootcamp at the University of Denver. Diverse experience analyzing and presenting data and maintaining successful customer relationships. Over 5 years of experience managing small teams. Eager to continue being a problem solver in a new way.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### ASSISTANT PROPERTY MANAGER

Briggs Development | 2021 - July 2022

- Maintained clear and friendly communication between tenants and vendors for 4 commercial properties.
- Receive, process and organize AP/AR
- Prepare lease abstracts, commencement letters, annual budget reports and presentations.

#### ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT

Storek, Carlson, & Strutz LLP | 2019 - 2021

- Corresponded with clients and their proxies, handled physical and digital confidential tax and financial information.
- Scheduled in person and virtual appointments for multiple accountants. Assembled physical and digital tax returns.
- Maintained extensive digital and analog filing systems.

# OFFICE MANAGER

Neale & Sons Appraisers and Auctioneers | 2016 - 2019

- Designed layout, content, and graphics for "nealeandsons.com" using WordPress. Maintained and updated content regularly.
- Client communication and scheduling. Formatting, editing, and submitting confidential appraisal reports to clients.
- Designing and launching promotional email campaigns.

## **EDUCATION**

### FULL STACK CODING BOOTCAMP

University of Denver | October 2022 - January 2023

# BA ENGLISH LITERATURE

UC Santa Barbara | 2003 - 2006

# LICENSE

REAL ESTATE AGENT, CA